<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications | Personal Academic Website</title>
    <link>https://example.com/publication/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Publications</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu7729264130191091259.png</url>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Object-Oriented Programming</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/preprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/preprint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project, I delved into the basics of object-oriented programming. In Python, I implemented:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Classes and methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inheritance and method overriding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using &lt;code&gt;super()&lt;/code&gt; to call a parent class&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Abstract classes and interfaces via the &lt;code&gt;abc&lt;/code&gt; module&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simple applications using classes, such as order simulation, library management, and geometric shape calculations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OOP helps structure code to make it scalable, understandable, and reusable. This approach is widely used in developing large, maintainable software systems. Working with OOP was a significant milestone in my professional growth as an aspiring programmer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management and Digital Transformation: Implementing IT Technologies in Business Processes</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/journal-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/journal-article/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In an environment of increasing project complexity and the need for rapid adaptation to change, implementing IT tools has become an essential component of effective project management. In my practice, I apply hybrid methodologies that combine elements of Agile, Kanban, and traditional approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Steps in Digital Transformation for Project Management:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automating planning and control processes using Notion and Trello.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Centralizing documentation storage and communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrating development and management tools (GitHub Projects).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visualizing progress and performance metrics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Systematizing task assignments, deadlines, and responsibilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These changes have reduced time spent on routine tasks, increased transparency for the team and clients, and improved quality control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital transformation is not limited to adopting a single tool—it represents a philosophy of continuous process improvement. My approach is built on openness to experimentation, adaptability, and continuous feedback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT Conference in Paris: New Horizons of Technology</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/conference-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/conference-paper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Tech &amp;amp; Innovation Summit Paris 2025&lt;/em&gt; conference took place at the modern Station F technology hub, gathering over 5,000 participants from around the world. The program was packed with events, from morning keynote speeches to evening networking sessions and hands-on workshops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highlights included:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A presentation by a Google expert on AI ethics and algorithm transparency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A panel discussion on cybersecurity in the age of quantum computing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workshops on creating sustainable software solutions using Python and Go.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also visited several startup booths showcasing innovations in healthcare, smart city infrastructure, and education. The conference atmosphere was inspiring and reminded me how rapidly technology evolves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event not only enriched my knowledge but also marked an important milestone in my professional journey as an aspiring developer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
